[
    {
      "level0": [
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 60000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": "Welcome to ** **\n\n"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "Which is the correct statement?\n\n`1-` \n`2-` \n`3-` ",
            "answers": ["2"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Great job! Now let's take a look at outputs to console"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 60000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": "**Output to Console!**\n\nLet’s learn how to output something to a console using the `` function.\n\n__Looking like this:__\n```language\n```"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**True, or false?**\n\nThe `` is a function in  which is used to print any kind of variables defined before in it or to just print any message that needs to be displayed.",
            "answers": ["✅"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 2,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "Wow!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 60000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 60000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
              "",
              "",
              ""
            ],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 1,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Good job!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 60000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 60000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**True, or false?**\n\n",
            "answers": ["✅"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 5,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "Wow!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 60000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**True, or false?**\n\n",
            "answers": ["✅"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 5,
            "xp": 8,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "Awesome!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**Answer with yes or no**\n\n",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Awesome! Good Job :=)"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": ["no"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 3,
            "premiumTries": 5,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Perfect!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**",
            "answers": ["no"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 3,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Double dice, congrats!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**True, or false?**\n\n",
            "answers": ["✅"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 2,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "Nice!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": ["✅"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "Nice!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Easy! Nice : ) "
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Awesome!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "*",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Thats right!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Congrats, your solution is correct!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 120000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Perfect! Double dice."
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 120000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Right!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Right!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 10,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Right!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 20,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Congrats!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": ["✅"],
            "time": 60000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 2,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "Nice!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ]
      ],
      "level1": [
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 20,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Perfect!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Good!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": "**"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**True, or false?**\n\n",
            "answers": ["❌"],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 2,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "That's true!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**",
            "answers": [""],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 5,
            "premiumTries": 10,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "answer",
            "correct": "Perfect!"
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "xp": 0,
            "time": 90000,
            "type": "continue",
            "answers": ["continue"],
            "question": ""
          }
        ],
        [
          {
            "question": "**True, or false?**\n\n",
            "answers": ["❌"],
            "time": 90000,
            "tries": 2,
            "premiumTries": 3,
            "xp": 5,
            "type": "reaction",
            "correct": "Awesome, congrats!"
          }
        ]
        
      ]
    }
  ]
  